[
     {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [52, 57, 56, 51, 55, 53, 57, 54, 57]?",
      "correctAnswer": "57",
      "options": [
        "56",
        "57",
        "58",
        "59"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [56, 57, 54, 55, 56, 52, 56, 56, 53, 58]?",
      "correctAnswer": "56",
      "options": [
        "55",
        "56",
        "57",
        "58"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [58, 58, 53, 58, 57, 55, 59, 58, 58, 56, 54]?",
      "correctAnswer": "58",
      "options": [
        "57",
        "58",
        "59",
        "60"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [55, 57, 56, 58, 55, 59, 55, 60, 54]?",
      "correctAnswer": "55",
      "options": [
        "54",
        "55",
        "56",
        "57"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [56, 58, 59, 61, 59, 60, 59, 57, 55, 59]?",
      "correctAnswer": "59",
      "options": [
        "58",
        "59",
        "60",
        "61"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [62, 61, 58, 62, 57, 59, 56, 62, 62, 62, 60]?",
      "correctAnswer": "62",
      "options": [
        "61",
        "62",
        "63",
        "64"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [63, 62, 59, 60, 63, 58, 61, 63, 57]?",
      "correctAnswer": "63",
      "options": [
        "62",
        "63",
        "64",
        "65"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [63, 62, 61, 60, 59, 60, 58, 60, 64, 60]?",
      "correctAnswer": "60",
      "options": [
        "59",
        "60",
        "61",
        "62"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [61, 61, 63, 61, 62, 59, 60, 61, 65, 64, 61]?",
      "correctAnswer": "61",
      "options": [
        "60",
        "61",
        "62",
        "63"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [63, 63, 64, 66, 60, 67, 61, 62, 63, 65]?",
      "correctAnswer": "63",
      "options": [
        "62",
        "63",
        "64",
        "65"
      ]
    }
]